[Neferpitou] Sire!
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
AN X INDEBTED X INSECT
[narrator] Youpi's attack succeeded
in splitting up the Extermination Team.
[limbs whipping]
[narrator] He completely destroyed
the central staircase
and stood ready to engage
anyone who dared climb it.
Behind him were Knuckle and Meleoron,
And below…
the ones hit at the closest range
by Youpi's attack were Shoot…
[narrator] …and Morel.
The rest is up to you.
Knuckle.
[narrator] He couldn't say
Knuckle's name out loud.
Huh?
This resistance…
That's not smoke.
Get back here. You fool!
[narrator] After using
his own weapon as a decoy,
Morel was left
with no alternative but to run.
However…
[Knuckle] Hakoware, Bankruptcy Chapter 7!
Damn. I'm giving it all I've got
to send him flying over the horizon…
but he's just at 590?
[groans] Ten seconds
feels like an eternity right now.
[narrator] Hakoware, Bankruptcy Chapter 7
accrues interest as time passes,
[narrator] Youpi was enraged,
but was brought back to his senses
Shoot realized
that this would be his signature move.
[growls]
[narrator] Sustained by adversity itself…
[Menthuthuyoupi] Hmm?
[narrator] …Shoot took flight.
[Morel] Shoot, Knuckle.
I wanna give you guys a big hug,
and that's the only way I can think of
to make you let me.
[narrator] The massive amount of dust
that was created
helped diffuse Morel's smoky aura
throughout the palace.
When Youpi destroyed the central stairway,
Gon and Killua evaded the attack,
Ikalgo's ability lets him control corpses
like parts of his own body.
[narrator] It was then
that Killua found himself running.
Huh?
[Killua] What am I doing?
What's wrong with me?
[narrator] Naturally, he was
rather perplexed at his own actions.
Although his mind was in a panic…
his body continued to act
in a rational manner,
Combining speed with the utmost accuracy,
he eliminated
the two soldier Ants' options,
as well as their ability to fight.
[Killua] Damn it.
What the hell?
What have I done?
[gasps]
[Ikalgo] Killua…
you owe me one.
[narrator] As he began
to return to his senses,
various emotions swirled
inside Killua's mind,
but Ikalgo's words
were just enough to dispel the chaos.
Killua was focused once again
and perfectly in control.
located at both ends.
Unfortunately, they were
currently occupied by soldier Ants.
Ikalgo raced past the two Ants
as quickly as possible,
and at the very moment
that he finally reached the elevator…
-[door opens]
-Hmm?
and from the darkness,
two figures emerged.
[Ikalgo] Cheetu.
And Bloster.
The two soldier Ants saw an enemy,
sent out an alert,
and then died immediately.
The intruder who killed them
went back to where he came from.
The time between that
and Flutter coming down the hall,
I mean, Leol's orders?
[Shaiapouf] How pathetic!
How do you qualify as a Royal Guard?
No.
He had an absolute ideal to live up to
with no room for amendment.
[Shaiapouf laughing hysterically]
Pouf, the former Royal Guard!
No, Pouf, scum of the earth,
the truth is
you just don't want to admit it.
You don't want him to be with that woman.
[narrator] His emotions were directed
at the King, as well as himself.
[Shaiapouf] An absolute King
feeling concern for a lowly human,
lowering himself to visiting the chambers
of human scum by choice.
You knew that much
even before you got here.
You fail as a Royal Guard
not because you didn't know
his whereabouts, far from it.
You fail, because you did know,
and in spite of that
you chose not to rush to his aid.
You're a traitor, Pouf.
You're lower than an insect.
You must devote yourself
solely to the King.
For the King. For the King.
For the King. For the King. For the King!
For the King!
[narrator] For a few brief seconds
after arriving in the throne room,
[Shaiapouf] I must go to the King's side.
Hey.
Ignoring me?
[thuds]
Going straight to the King's side, huh?
Too bad for you.
I've got you closed in.
[Shaiapouf] Then I must ask,
would you please let me out?
[Shaiapouf] Spiritual Message!
He said he'd use it
to keep Pouf away from the King.
If it's covering
the entire third floor of the tower,
then the King and Pitou aren't there.
So where are they?
[gasps]
[wind blowing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Divide and Conquer".
No! I don t want to leave you!
[Killua] It's okay.
We're connected by an invisible bond.